addoninteractive.com 2019-03-05

# AddonChat Chat Software - HTML5 Chat and Instant Messaging Software - Privacy Policy

AddonChat is a full-featured HTML5 real-time Chat and Instant Messaging Solution. Provide Real Time Chat To Your Site's Visitors. 

We respect your privacy, and the privacy of your users. 

This privacy policy applies to all web sites owned and maintained by AddonInteractive. We may be reached via e-mail at [support@addonchat.com](mailto:support@addonchat.com). Please contact us if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, or the manner in which AddonInteractive uses any information collected from you. 

AddonInteractive may collect personally identifiable information from site visitors, and visitors using provided web applications. AddonInteractive may also receive personal information from our partners. AddonInteractive requires the following information when registering for an account: 

  * e-Mail Address
  * Company Name / Organization if applicable
  * User specified password
  * User Name

AddonInteractive may request, but not require, the following information when creating an account with us: 

  * Web Site Address
  * Description of Chat Room
  * Full Name
  * Birth Date and/or age
  * Primary & Secondary Phone Numbers
  * Operational Language
  * Would you like to be listed in our directory
  * Would you like us to send you e-mail notices
  * For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by e-mailing us at the address provided above. Please include your account ID number when contacting us. AddonInteractive will not contact those who opt out of our e-mail notices. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us only when requested to discuss specific account details, or for technical support assistance. 

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mail as at the address provided above. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

Services provided by AddonInteractive are intended for individuals age 13 and over only. We do not provide content for children. Parents should closely monitor content visited by children, and review privacy policies on all web sites to determine whether content is acceptable for children. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above e-mail address.
